downloadinator.com 2014-08-25

# Privacy Policy

##  PRIVACY POLICY

Safe Updates Technology takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about Safe Updates Technology's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how Safe Updates Technology receives, collects and uses information in connection with our website and software provided on the website (the website and software collectively referred to herein as "Site"). 

###  Collection and Use of Information

Safe Updates Technology does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail, age, gender, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information"). 

Safe Updates Technology may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are on Safe Updates Technology's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout as well as for other customer service purposes. Safe Updates Technology's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information. 

Safe Updates Technology may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. Safe Updates Technology collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. Safe Updates Technology will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users. 

###  Sharing and Disclosure of Information

Safe Updates Technology does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. Safe Updates Technology may disclose your Personal Information if Safe Updates Technology believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Safe Updates Technology (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Safe Updates Technology (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Safe Updates Technology services or members of the public. 

###  Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the Safe Updates Technology website and software and must LEAVE immediately. 

###  Explicit Content

You understand that by using the Service, you may encounter content that may be deemed offensive, indecent, or objectionable, which content may or may not be identified as having explicit language. Nevertheless, you agree to use the Site at your sole risk and that Safe Updates Technology shall have no liability to you for content that may be found to be offensive, indecent, or objectionable. Safe Updates Technology shall have no liability or responsibility to you for any content or materials that may be available in connection with the Site that you might find objectionable. 

###  Security

Safe Updates Technology takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although Safe Updates Technology cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, Safe Updates Technology has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. 

###  Changes to Policy

From time to time, Safe Updates Technology may revise this Policy. Safe Updates Technology will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information Safe Updates Technology collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed.
